<![CDATA[我好饿
I get so hungry.]]>
<![CDATA[我把报警电话设成快捷键了
Just so you know, 911's on speed-dial.]]>
<![CDATA[克丽丝 你可以相信我 这么说你爸上路了
Krissy,you can trust me. So your dad's on the road right now?]]>
<![CDATA[有一阵了吗
Been gone a while?]]>
<![CDATA[我爸爸走了 还没回来
My dad left, and he didn't come back.]]>
<![CDATA[所以我要跟你一去
So I'm coming with you.]]>
<![CDATA[-不 绝对不行  -我要去
-No. Hell,no.  -I'm coming!]]>
<![CDATA[那个女招待为什么要进卡车
Why is that waitress getting into that truck?]]>
<![CDATA[好了 承认吧 干得不错
All right. Come on. Give it up. Good work.]]>
<![CDATA[你是个笨蛋
You're a dweeb.]]>
<![CDATA[坚持住 我来救你 迪恩
Hold on --I got you! Dean!]]>
<![CDATA[他帮不了你 没人救得了
He can't help you. No one can.]]>
<![CDATA[那我就自己动手
I guess I'll have to help myself,then.]]>
<![CDATA[我要退休了
I'm retiring.]]>
<![CDATA[-我们真逊  -没错
-We're so lame.  -Yeah,we are.]]>
<![CDATA[多保重
Take care of yourself.]]>
<![CDATA[刚才是什么
what was that?]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What?]]>
<![CDATA[这里只有我们 克丽丝
there's no one out here but us,krissy.]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What?]]>
<![CDATA[不 不要
no,no. No,no,no.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[不 别把我丢这里 艾登
No. No. Don't leave me here! Aidan!]]>
<![CDATA[别把我丢这里
Don't leave me here!]]>
<![CDATA[天啊
oh,god.]]>
<![CDATA[你没事吧
You okay?]]>
<![CDATA[真险
That was close.]]>
<![CDATA[下次你当诱饵吧
Next time one of you can be the bait.]]>
<![CDATA[就是他
It's him.]]>
<![CDATA[搞定一个 还剩下两个
One down. Two to go.]]>
<![CDATA[我们这次是什么案子
So,what are we looking at again?]]>
<![CDATA[两位年轻女性命丧高速公路附近
"two young women found near the freeway]]>
<![CDATA[喉部被撕裂
With their throats ripped out."]]>
<![CDATA[在我看来像吸血鬼所为
Sounds vampy to me.]]>
<![CDATA[是啊 也许
Yeah,maybe.]]>
<![CDATA[如果你这个案子你想休息一下
Listen,if you want to take a knee on this one]]>
<![CDATA[觉得不太舒服...
If you're not feeling up to it...]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What?]]>
<![CDATA[你懂的 那些考验 卡斯说过的
You know,the trials, what cass said,]]>
<![CDATA[你有他治愈不了的问题
That you got what he can't cure.]]>
<![CDATA[到底是什么
which means what, exactly?]]>
<![CDATA[我不知道 你告诉我 你没事吧
Well,I don't know. You tell me. Are you okay?]]>
<![CDATA[我没事 你呢
I'm fine. Are you okay?]]>
<![CDATA[我
Me?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊 卡斯把你打得挺惨
Yeah. cass dinged you up pretty good.]]>
<![CDATA[然后呢
And?]]>
<![CDATA[我就想确定你没事
And I just wanted to make sure you're okay.]]>
<![CDATA[什么 我的感觉吗
What, like my feelings?]]>
<![CDATA[如果你想说这事 当然可以
If that's what you want to talk about,sure.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[这样吧
I'll tell you what.]]>
<![CDATA[不如我去喝点薄荷茶
Why don't I go get some, herbal tea.]]>
<![CDATA[然后你可以联系个吸毒的什么的
Okay.And you can find some cowboy junkies on the dial.]]>
<![CDATA[不干 迪恩
Eat me,dean.]]>
<![CDATA[然后我们好好谈谈
And you know what? We'll just talk it out.]]>
<![CDATA[不错
Good talk.]]>
<![CDATA[不对 是棒极了 非常健康
Nay,great talk! Very healthy!]]>
<![CDATA[联邦调查局的
Fbi?]]>
<![CDATA[你们是来调查少女杀手谋杀案的吗
You're here about the lady killer murders,aren't you?]]>
<![CDATA[少女杀手谋杀案
The lady killer murders?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊 我自己编的
Yeah, coined it myself.]]>
<![CDATA[名字不错 有什么线索
Congratulations. What can you tell us?]]>
<![CDATA[两位受害者都是女性 不到二十一岁
Well,both Victims were female, under 21,]]>
<![CDATA[关键是
And here's the kicker --]]>
<![CDATA[她们的血都被吸干了
They were drained of all their blood.]]>
<![CDATA[没错 我们也觉得很奇怪
Exactly. We found that strange,also.]]>
<![CDATA[可昨晚 事情就更奇怪了
But then last night, things got even stranger.]]>
<![CDATA[-昨晚  -没错
-Last night?  -Yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[出于安全目的 我们在所有角度
We set up a security cam on fuller's point]]>
<![CDATA[安装了监控
For safety purposes.]]>
<![CDATA[本地年轻人喜欢亲热的地方
It's where our local young people like to go make out.]]>
<![CDATA[昨晚 事情变得很疯狂
Last night, things got crazy.]]>
<![CDATA[真见鬼 是吗
Hell of a thing, ain't it?]]>
<![CDATA[确认他们身份了吗
you I.D. Any of these people?]]>
<![CDATA[还没有
Well,not yet.]]>
<![CDATA[当我们到的时候 犯罪现场空无一物
Crime scene was empty when we got there.]]>
<![CDATA[没有受害者 什么都没有
No Vic,no nothing.]]>
<![CDATA[我想是不是跟邪教或者毒品有关
I'm thinking it's some kind of cult or a drug thing.]]>
<![CDATA[所以一小时前 我在全州
So I put a statewide a.P.B. Out on these three]]>
<![CDATA[对他们三个下了通缉
About an hour ago.]]>
<![CDATA[我需要你取消通缉
I'm gonna need you to call that off.]]>
<![CDATA[我们需要这个录像
And we're gonna need this footage.]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What?]]>
<![CDATA[警长 你觉得我们为什么来这里
Sheriff, why do you think we're here?]]>
<![CDATA[这个涉及到联邦调查局的案子
You just crossed streams with a federal investigation.]]>
<![CDATA[现在 我建议你跟我们合作 取消通缉
Now,I suggest you cooperate, call off your a.P.B.,]]>
<![CDATA[否则后果会很严重的
Or you're gonna find yourself in a world of hurt.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧
Right.]]>
<![CDATA[怎么回事 伙计
So,what was that all about,g-man?]]>
<![CDATA[还记得克丽丝 钱伯斯吗
You remember krissy chambers?]]>
<![CDATA[记得 菲特拉斯那桩案子 对吗
Uh,yeah,the vetalas case, right?]]>
<![CDATA[他们当时在打高速公路旁停车场的主意
They were working that truck stop by the freeway.]]>
<![CDATA[她和她爸爸帮我们把他们击退
She and her dad helped us shut 'em down.]]>
<![CDATA[对啊 然后他许诺做普通老百姓
Right,and then he promised to go civilian]]>
<![CDATA[这样她长大 就不会猎魔了
So she wouldn't grow up to be a hunter.]]>
<![CDATA[猜猜谁是这场凶杀电影主角
Well,guess who the star of this snuff film is?]]>
<![CDATA[别这样
Come on.]]>
<![CDATA[也许他不知道 她在干这个
Well,maybe he doesn't know she's doing this.]]>
<![CDATA[什么 半夜偷偷溜出来
What,sneaking out in the middle of the night]]>
<![CDATA[跟一帮乳臭未干的小孩一起猎魔吗
To go hunt monsters with the apple dumpling gang?]]>
<![CDATA[这年头小孩都这么玩闹吗
Is that what kids are doing for kicks these days?]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 也许他知道 他帮着他一起
Okay. Then maybe he knows, and he's helping her out.]]>
<![CDATA[什么 还上了监控录像
What,get caught on "candid camera"?]]>
<![CDATA[趁她没有惹更多麻烦 赶紧找到她
Let's just go find her before she gets into any more trouble.]]>
<![CDATA[你二十五岁吗
You're 25?]]>
<![CDATA[实际上 我觉得我是四十岁
Actually, I think I'm 40.]]>
<![CDATA[我告诉你 我有男朋友的
I told you... I have a boyfriend.]]>
<![CDATA[那你手机里怎么没有他的电话
Then how come I couldn't find him in your cellie?]]>
<![CDATA[因为我们就网聊
Because we only skype.]]>
<![CDATA[对啊 让我猜猜 他也住在加拿大
Right. And let me guess -- he also lives in canada?]]>
<![CDATA[确实是这样
You know,he does, actually. Oh.]]>
<![CDATA[一座小镇 叫"去死吧"
A small town called "kiss my ass."]]>
<![CDATA[好吧
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[可是...
But...]]>
<![CDATA[之前在车里 你的感觉不是这样的
You sure were giving off a different vibe in the car.]]>
<![CDATA[好 你回来了 我们开始吧
Good. You're back. Let's do this.]]>
<![CDATA[最后一次看到吸血鬼
Vamp was last seen by an atm camera]]>
<![CDATA[是酒店登记处取款机的摄像头
Checking into this hotel.]]>
<![CDATA[我黑进了酒店的监控录像 找到了他
I tapped into the hotel's security cams and found him.]]>
<![CDATA[215房间
Room 215.]]>
<![CDATA[好的
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[我们动手吧
Let's do this.]]>
<![CDATA[镜头带好了吗
You transmitting?]]>
<![CDATA[当然
You bet.]]>
<![CDATA[他独自行动的吗
He alone?]]>
<![CDATA[没法说
I can't tell.]]>
<![CDATA[我们开始个新传统如何
Hey,how about we start a new tradition,]]>
<![CDATA[每次行动前 我们互相来个好运吻
And before each job,we give each other good-luck kisses?]]>
<![CDATA[我揍你一顿如何
How about I punch you in the throat instead?]]>
<![CDATA[你知道 你这样黏糊糊的缠着克丽丝
You know you're not gonna get anywhere with krissy]]>
<![CDATA[不会有结果的
With those cheesy moves.]]>
<![CDATA[你别搅和我的好事
How about you stop putting salt in my game]]>
<![CDATA[管好你自己如何
And mind your own business?]]>
<![CDATA[血迹
Blood?]]>
<![CDATA[嘿 克丽丝
Hey,krissy.]]>
<![CDATA[你们俩来这里干什么
What are you two doing here?]]>
<![CDATA[救你啊
Saving your bacon, that's what.]]>
<![CDATA[我需要你们救我吗
Does it look like my bacon needs saving?]]>
<![CDATA[等一下 你们怎么找到我的 我用的都是现金
Wait. How'd you find me? I paid cash everywhere.]]>
<![CDATA[这方圆二十英里 只有两家酒店
Only two hotels within a 20-mile radius,]]>
<![CDATA[我们也付的是现金 比你的还多
And we paid cash,too -- just more.]]>
<![CDATA[该死的家伙
Freaking clerk.]]>
<![CDATA[克丽丝 你爸爸呢
Krissy, where's your dad?]]>
<![CDATA[死了
Dead.]]>
<![CDATA[我们再来一次分手 永不见面
Well,let's do this again, like,never.]]>
<![CDATA[现在走吧 我们有事情要做
Now go. We got this.]]>
<![CDATA[我们什么
We who?]]>
<![CDATA[抓到什么了
And got what?]]>
<![CDATA[吸血鬼
A vampire.]]>
<![CDATA[对不起 什么
Sorry. A what?]]>
<![CDATA[我们进来了 房间里没人
We're in. The room's clear.]]>
<![CDATA[只有一个受害者
Nobody here but a Vic.]]>
<![CDATA[我抓住他了
I got him!]]>
<![CDATA[你
You --]]>
<![CDATA[你个狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.]]>
<![CDATA[我们需要叫救护车 马上就到
We need to call an ambulance! Ambulance is on its way.]]>
<![CDATA[她休克了 我给她用镇静剂
She's in shock. I'll stabilize her.]]>
<![CDATA[把她留给护理人员吧
We'll leave her here for the paramedics.]]>
<![CDATA[求你了 别杀我
Please! Don't shoot me!]]>
<![CDATA[别开枪 求你了
Don't shoot me! Please,don't --]]>
<![CDATA[求你了 好疼啊
Please... It hurts so bad!]]>
<![CDATA[你怎么这么快就把他搞定了
How did you drop him so quickly?]]>
<![CDATA[沾过死人血的飞镖
Darts filled with dead man's blood.]]>
<![CDATA[那辆蓝色厢车呢
Where's the blue van?]]>
<![CDATA[什么蓝色厢车
What blue van?]]>
<![CDATA[他用来逃跑的蓝色厢车
The blue van that he was usain bolting it to?]]>
<![CDATA[没事了
Never mind.]]>
<![CDATA[等一下 住手
Wait,stop!]]>
<![CDATA[你不能动手
This is not your kill.]]>
<![CDATA[你在说什么
What are you talking about?]]>
<![CDATA[三个月前 这个吸血鬼溜进了一户人家
Three months ago,this blood banger snuck into a house]]>
<![CDATA[杀死了三个熟睡的人
And killed three people in their sleep.]]>
<![CDATA[什么 不 这不是我干的
What?! No! I didn't do that!]]>
<![CDATA[其中一个是从没伤害过任何人的女人
One was a woman -- never hurt anyone!]]>
<![CDATA[另外两个是弟弟 妹妹
The other two, a brother and a sister.]]>
<![CDATA[我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.]]>
<![CDATA[从朋友家回来 我发现了他们
I came home from a friend's house,and I found them.]]>
<![CDATA[他们是我的家人
they were my family!]]>
<![CDATA[不是我干的
This isn't happening.]]>
<![CDATA[我什么都没干 我发誓
I didn't do anything, I swear.]]>
<![CDATA[求你了 帮帮我
Please,help me!]]>
<![CDATA[没事了
It's okay.]]>
<![CDATA[都结束了
It's over.]]>
<![CDATA[我们需要私下里跟你谈谈
We need to talk to you privately.]]>
<![CDATA[你认识他吗
You know this guy?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊 我们以前认识
Yeah. We have a past.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 跟我们讲讲发生了什么
All right. So,you're gonna have to catch me up.]]>
<![CDATA[什么 你父亲
What -- did your dad,uh --]]>
<![CDATA[他没法不过那样的生活 对吗
He couldn't quit the life, could he?]]>
<![CDATA[不是的
No,he did.]]>
<![CDATA[有一段时间 我们很开心
For a while, it was amazing.]]>
<![CDATA[每晚都一起吃晚饭
We had dinner every night at a table.]]>
<![CDATA[看电视 散步 甚至还去逛商场
We watched tv,went on walks. Even went to the mall.]]>
<![CDATA[然后呢
And then?]]>
<![CDATA[然后 过去再度袭来
And then, the past came a-knockin'.]]>
<![CDATA[一天早晨我醒来 发现他死了...
I woke up one morning and found him dead....]]>
<![CDATA[喉咙被撕裂
...His throat ripped out.]]>
<![CDATA[我很难过
Well,I'm sorry.]]>
<![CDATA[我也是
Me too.]]>
<![CDATA[如果不是有约瑟芬和艾登
If it weren't for Josephine and Aidan,]]>
<![CDATA[我都不知道要怎么活下来
I don't know how I would have made it.]]>
<![CDATA[那 他俩也都失去了家人 是吗
So,they both lost their families,as well?]]>
<![CDATA[我们一起猎杀吸血鬼
Yeah,the same vamps we're hunting together --]]>
<![CDATA[一窝呢
A nest.]]>
<![CDATA[抱歉 不是我想扫你们的兴
Well,look,I am sorry to rain on your parade,]]>
<![CDATA[但你们太年轻 不该做这些
But you are way too young to be doing this.]]>
<![CDATA[猎魔杀鬼 我们才不年轻
You're never too young to kill monsters,]]>
<![CDATA[尤其他们还跟你有灭门之仇
Especially the ones that kill your family.]]>
<![CDATA[猎魔不是为了杀戮或复仇
Hunting isn't all about killing and revenge.]]>
<![CDATA[我以为上次我们已经谈过了
I thought we had this chat last time.]]>
<![CDATA[你还有...
Do you have any,uh --]]>
<![CDATA[你还有任何亲戚吗
Do you have any family that's still out there?]]>
<![CDATA[辛辛那提有个姨妈 怎么
An aunt in cincinnati. Why?]]>
<![CDATA[你去收拾行李 我们送你过去
'cause you're packing a bag, and we're taking you there.]]>
<![CDATA[我觉得维克多不会同意的
I think Victor's gonna have a problem with that.]]>
<![CDATA[维克多
Victor?]]>
<![CDATA[他带我们入行 教我们一切
He took us in, showed us everything we know.]]>
<![CDATA[等等 这说的是什么
Wait. So, what are we talking here?]]>
<![CDATA[猎魔人培训学校吗
Some sort of kid's school for hunters?]]>
<![CDATA[别傻了吧唧的好吗 我们又不是X战警
Don't be such a dweeb,okay? We're not the x-men.]]>
<![CDATA[维克多在帮助我们复仇
Victor's helping us get revenge.]]>
<![CDATA[我不管他在干什么 他都混蛋
Yeah,well,I don't care what he is. He sucks.]]>
<![CDATA[因为你们几个人还是被抓了
'cause you and your little crew here got caught.]]>
<![CDATA[如果抓你们的不是我
And if it wasn't for me,]]>
<![CDATA[你们的脸现在都是头条新闻
Your faces would be splattered all over the news.]]>
<![CDATA[那又如何
Well,you know, so what?!]]>
<![CDATA[也许是时候让大众知晓
Maybe it's time that people know the truth]]>
<![CDATA[夜幕下都在发生什么了
About what's really going bump in the night.]]>
<![CDATA[然后造成恐慌 导致混乱吗
Oh,and cause panic? Create mayhem?]]>
<![CDATA[不错 是个好计划
Yeah, that's a great plan.]]>
<![CDATA[我用不着你来救我 迪恩
Look,I don't need you to save me,Dean.]]>
<![CDATA[我不再是孩子了
I'm not a little kid anymore.]]>
<![CDATA[什么情况
What happened?]]>
<![CDATA[少年人 就这样
Teenagers,that's what.]]>
<![CDATA[-她跟你说起维克多了吗  -说了 你觉得呢
-She tell you about Victor?  -Yeah. What do we think?]]>
<![CDATA[我们以前在斯波坎是不是遇到过
Well,didn't we meet up with a hunter named Victor]]>
<![CDATA[一个叫维克多的猎魔人
One time in Spokane?]]>
<![CDATA[那可是很久之前了
That's a long time ago.]]>
<![CDATA[从那之后就没有他的消息
I haven't heard about him since.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 那这些孩子...
All right, so,these kids are --]]>
<![CDATA[危险又疯狂 可不是呢
Dangerous and off their meds? Yeah,no kidding.]]>
<![CDATA[怎么 咱们去找那个维克多谈谈
So,what? We go and talk with Victor?]]>
<![CDATA[准备好了吗
Ready?]]>
<![CDATA[好了
okay.]]>
<![CDATA[没想到是这么个地方
Not what I'd call a compound.]]>
<![CDATA[怎么了
What's wrong?]]>
<![CDATA[只是没想到是这样的
It's just not what I expected.]]>
<![CDATA[那你以为是什么样
And what was that?]]>
<![CDATA[更有"苍蝇王"的范(小说名)
A little more "lord of the flies""]]>
<![CDATA[而不是如此"考斯比"范(电视剧天才老爹)
Less Huxtables.]]>
<![CDATA[抱歉让你失望了
Sorry to disappoint.]]>
<![CDATA[我是维克多 罗杰斯
Victor rogers.]]>
<![CDATA[我们见过 那时候在华盛顿猎魔
We met --a rugaru hunt in washington.]]>
<![CDATA[我是山姆 他是迪恩
I'm Sam. This is Dean.]]>
<![CDATA[想起来了 温彻斯特兄弟
Oh,yes. The winchesters.]]>
<![CDATA[对
Right.]]>
<![CDATA[-好点了吗  -好多了
-Better now?  -Much.]]>
<![CDATA[我们总是怎么说来着
And what do we always say?]]>
<![CDATA[前进 但从不遗忘
Move on, but never forget.]]>
<![CDATA[很好 你明早不是还有个小考吗
Good. Now,don't you have a trig test in the morning?]]>
<![CDATA[我很好 维克 也没小考
Oh,I'm good,Vic. No test.]]>
<![CDATA[我要去爽一下 玩玩电游
I'm just gonna chill, play video games.]]>
<![CDATA[你就做梦吧
Yeah,keep dreaming.]]>
<![CDATA[我说了两次 让你打扫房间
Because I asked you to clean your room twice,]]>
<![CDATA[你都还没干完呢
And you still haven't done it.]]>
<![CDATA[快去
Go on.]]>
<![CDATA[还有你
And you.]]>
<![CDATA[明早 这次猎杀行动的报告交到你桌上
A full report about the hunt on your desk by morning.]]>
<![CDATA[好了 我回房了
Okay. I'll be in my room.]]>
<![CDATA[喝点什么吗
Drink?]]>
<![CDATA[好的
Sure.]]>
<![CDATA[孩子们去上学吗
So, these kids go to school --]]>
<![CDATA[就是真正的那种学校
Like,school-school, real school?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊 在经历那么多事情后
Yes,and they're doing incredibly well]]>
<![CDATA[他们学习还真都不错
Considering all they've been through.]]>
<![CDATA[那 这是怎么回事
Okay, so how does this work?]]>
<![CDATA[在足球训练结束后
What,after -- after soccer practice]]>
<![CDATA[也卖完了糕点
And -- and the bake sale,]]>
<![CDATA[他们就去砍吸血鬼的脑袋吗
They,uh, chop vampires' heads off?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊
Well,yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[我觉得均衡发展很重要 不是吗
I think a balanced approach is best,don't you?]]>
<![CDATA[但他们还是孩子
But they're kids.]]>
<![CDATA[根本就不该去猎魔
They shouldn't be hunting at all.]]>
<![CDATA[你得赶快停手
You got to break this up right now.]]>
<![CDATA[我找到他们的时候 他们迷茫 困惑而愤怒
When I found them, they were lost,confused,angry.]]>
<![CDATA[我给了他们一个家 还有目标
I gave them family and purpose.]]>
<![CDATA[而你想把这一切都夺走 为什么
And you want to take all that away? Why?]]>
<![CDATA[这样他们就不会送命
So they don't get killed.]]>
<![CDATA[他们知道有风险
They know the risks.]]>
<![CDATA[是 但他们为什么要冒险
Yeah, but why take them?]]>
<![CDATA[因为下一代的猎魔人必须更优秀
Because the next generation of hunters has to be better.]]>
<![CDATA[比什么优秀
Better than what?]]>
<![CDATA[比我们
Better than us.]]>
<![CDATA[得了吧 伙计们
oh,come on,guys.]]>
<![CDATA[我认识你们的朋友 那个马丁疯了
I know your friends. I mean,Martin was insane.]]>
<![CDATA[至于那个加斯 显然小时候
And somebody obviously dropped Garth on his head]]>
<![CDATA[脑袋被门夹过
When he was a baby.]]>
<![CDATA[我知道你们很爱那个叫鲍比的
And I know you two loved that Bobby guy,]]>
<![CDATA[但他不过也就是个无能的酒鬼
But he was a barely functional alcoholic.]]>
<![CDATA[怎么说话呢
Watch it.]]>
<![CDATA[无意冒犯 但约瑟芬是
No disrespect meant, but Josephine is]]>
<![CDATA[州田径队选手 全国优秀学生
An all-state athlete and national merit scholar.]]>
<![CDATA[艾登速度极快 眨眼之间
Aidan is so fast he could pick your pocket]]>
<![CDATA[就能扒了你的口袋
Before you could even blink.]]>
<![CDATA[至于克丽丝
And Krissy,]]>
<![CDATA[她是个天生的领导和猎魔人
Oh she's just a natural-born leader and hunter.]]>
<![CDATA[那又如何
So what?]]>
<![CDATA[这三个孩子是精英
So these kids are the cream of the crop.]]>
<![CDATA[他们是梦幻般的组合 堪比披头士乐队
They are the beatles. They are the dream team.]]>
<![CDATA[等到他们大仇得报
And once they get their revenge...]]>
<![CDATA[他们会是你们想都想不到的优秀猎魔人
...They'll be better hunters than any of us ever dreamed of.]]>
<![CDATA[太疯狂了
This is crazy.]]>
<![CDATA[是吗 他们日子过得不错
Is it? They got a pretty good life.]]>
<![CDATA[孩子不该去猎魔 山姆
Kids aren't supposed to hunt,Sam.]]>
<![CDATA[咱俩当初不就是
We did.]]>
<![CDATA[是 所以看看咱们现在什么样
Yeah,and look what that did for us.]]>
<![CDATA[也许他们能过得好
Well,maybe they're doing it right.]]>
<![CDATA[也许他们能既猎魔 又过上真正的生活
Maybe they can hunt and have a real life.]]>
<![CDATA[你知道那不可能
You know that's not true.]]>
<![CDATA[为什么 因为咱们没做到吗
Why,'cause it didn't work for us?]]>
<![CDATA[因为任何人都做不到
Because it doesn't work for anybody.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 那你想怎么办
Okay,then what do you want to do?]]>
<![CDATA[维克多不可能就此停手的
'cause Victor's not gonna stop this.]]>
<![CDATA[-他们说有一窝吸血鬼要猎杀 是吗  -是
-They said they were hunting a nest,right?  -Yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[那咱们替他们收拾了吧
Well, let's hunt it for 'em.]]>
<![CDATA[这样 在咱们想到办法
Well,that way, until we can figure out]]>
<![CDATA[解决好维克多之前 他们都还安全
What to do with Victor, they stay safe.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧...
All right,um...]]>
<![CDATA[你打算怎么行动
So,what's your move?]]>
<![CDATA[我要去找那个被绑在酒店的姑娘谈谈
I want to talk to that girl who was tied up at the hotel.]]>
<![CDATA[有些事觉得不太对劲
Something didn't smell right about that.]]>
<![CDATA[不如你留在这 盯住"脱线家族"(美剧名)
Why don't you stay here and look after the brady bunch?]]>
<![CDATA[山姆 时间刚刚好
Sam,just in time.]]>
<![CDATA[-坐吧  -华夫饼吗
-Grab a seat.  -Waffles?]]>
<![CDATA[是 克丽丝的最爱
Yeah,Krissy's fav.]]>
<![CDATA[以前 我爸爸总给我做这个吃
My dad used to make 'em for me all the time.]]>
<![CDATA[我觉得 他大概只会做这一样
I think it was the only thing he knew how to cook.]]>
<![CDATA[专心吃
Interact.]]>
<![CDATA[对 书呆子
Yeah,nerd.]]>
<![CDATA[还有你 注意形象
And you --manners.]]>
<![CDATA[我们要迟到了
We're gonna be late.]]>
<![CDATA[快点
Come on.]]>
<![CDATA[拿好东西
Grab your stuff.]]>
<![CDATA[-放学后我去接你  -回见
-I'll pick you up after school.  -See ya.]]>
<![CDATA[像阵风一样 是吗
Whirlwind,right?]]>
<![CDATA[孩子们就是那样的
It's always like that with kids.]]>
<![CDATA[你有孩子吗
You got any?]]>
<![CDATA[我吗 没有
Me? Uh,no.]]>
<![CDATA[想要孩子吗
You want any?]]>
<![CDATA[不知道
Uh,I don't know.]]>
<![CDATA[相信我 答案是肯定的
Trust me, the answer's yes.]]>
<![CDATA[你的孩子吗
These yours?]]>
<![CDATA[是
Yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[直到我们去露营
Well, until we went camping]]>
<![CDATA[雪怪把他们撕成碎片
And a wendigo ripped them to shreds.]]>
<![CDATA[抱歉
Sorry.]]>
<![CDATA[所以你才这么做 收养这群孩子
Is that why you're doing this, taking all these kids in?]]>
<![CDATA[但你知道我怎么想的 山姆 这些孩子
But you know what I realized, Sam,is that these kids,]]>
<![CDATA[他们不用那样生活
They don't have to live it the way we have.]]>
<![CDATA[住糟糕的旅店房间 总是搬来搬去
You know,crappy hotel rooms, always moving,]]>
<![CDATA[没有家人 没有生活
No family,no life.]]>
<![CDATA[那不是必经之路
It's not the only way.]]>
<![CDATA[我已经和警察说了
Like I told the cops already,]]>
<![CDATA[我不确定为什么吉米 戴会做那样的事
I'm not sure why jimmy day would do something like this.]]>
<![CDATA[吉米 戴
Jimmy day?]]>
<![CDATA[等下 所以你认识抓你的人
Wait,so you knew the guy that grabbed you?]]>
<![CDATA[镇里的人都知道吉米 他是个英雄
Everyone in town knows jimmy. He's a hero.]]>
<![CDATA[他从阿富汗回来的时候
We had a parade for him downtown]]>
<![CDATA[我们还在市区为他游行
When he came back from afghanistan.]]>
<![CDATA[抱歉 什么时候的事
Uh,sorry. When was this?]]>
<![CDATA[几周前
A few weeks ago.]]>
<![CDATA[这个吉米 戴
So,uh... This jimmy day guy,]]>
<![CDATA[他 就是抓住你 把你带到旅店
He --he just grabbed you and took you to the hotel?]]>
<![CDATA[不是
No.]]>
<![CDATA[这个蓝色厢式车停下来的时候
I-I came from work and was in the parking lot]]>
<![CDATA[我刚下班 在停车场
When this blue van pulled up.]]>
<![CDATA[有个穿连帽衫的人问我路
This guy with a hoodie asked me directions.]]>
<![CDATA[我只记得这些 之后我醒来时被绑在床上
That's all I remember, till I woke up tied to that bed.]]>
<![CDATA[那个穿连帽衫的人也在吗
And was hoodie there, too?]]>
<![CDATA[只有吉米 他在哭 说他很抱歉
Just jimmy,and he was crying, saying he was sorry and all.]]>
<![CDATA[他很抱歉吗
That he was sorry?]]>
<![CDATA[一开始我以为他要杀了我
At first I thought he was gonna kill me.]]>
<![CDATA[但后来 他... 只是看上去很害怕
But then he just... He just seemed scared.]]>
<![CDATA[学校发生什么事了
Hey. What happened to school?]]>
<![CDATA[维克多接我们回来的
Victor pulled us out.]]>
<![CDATA[为什么
Why?]]>
<![CDATA[因为我们发现了另一个目标
'cause we've found another target.]]>
<![CDATA[谁
Who?]]>
<![CDATA[杀了克丽丝爸爸的贱人
The vamp that killed Krissy's dad.]]>
<![CDATA[准备好了吗
You ready?]]>
<![CDATA[好的
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[从附近的加油站拿到的安保录像
Pulled this from a security camera at a nearby gas station.]]>
<![CDATA[等下 我们怎么知道肯定是她
Wait,how do we know this is definitely her?]]>
<![CDATA[警方的素描 受害人的账户
Police sketch, Victim's accounts...]]>
<![CDATA[还有这个
...And this.]]>
<![CDATA[我爸的项链
My dad's necklace.]]>
<![CDATA[他们周年纪念的时候我妈妈给他的
My mom gave it to him on their anniversary.]]>
<![CDATA[你确定这是监视录像照片吗
Are you sure this is a video surveillance pic?]]>
<![CDATA[是她
It's her!]]>
<![CDATA[抱歉
Excuse me.]]>
<![CDATA[你在吗
Hey. You there?]]>
<![CDATA[是 那个女孩那边怎么样
Yeah. How did it go with the girl?]]>
<![CDATA[很奇怪 也许那个吸血鬼没说谎
Strange. Might be that vampire wasn't lying.]]>
<![CDATA[他才做吸血鬼一个月
He was fresh made within the month,]]>
<![CDATA[但是约瑟芬的家人三个月之前被谋杀了
But Josephine's family was murdered three months ago.]]>
<![CDATA[谁杀的
So,who killed them, then?]]>
<![CDATA[不知道
I don't know.]]>
<![CDATA[我想和那个开蓝色厢车的人聊聊
I'd like to talk to whoever's driving that blue van.]]>
<![CDATA[其他嘛 你呢
Other than that...You?]]>
<![CDATA[有事发生了
Something's up.]]>
<![CDATA[维克多说他有监控照片
Victor says he has a surveillance photo]]>
<![CDATA[拍到了杀死克丽丝父亲的吸血鬼
Of the vampire that killed Krissy's father.]]>
<![CDATA[但是 迪恩 我不确定
But,Dean... I'm not so sure.]]>
<![CDATA[为什么
Why's that?]]>
<![CDATA[没有时间戳
There's no time stamp on it.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 所以你觉得他说谎了
Okay. So you think he's lying?]]>
<![CDATA[或者只是他错了 很难说
Well,that,or he's just wrong. It's hard to say.]]>
<![CDATA[是 我从没相信过穿毛衣的人
Yeah,I never trust a guy who wears a sweater.]]>
<![CDATA[你想让我回去吗
You want me to head back there?]]>
<![CDATA[不 我可以 让我再研究下
No,no. I'm good. Let me do some more digging.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 我要跟旅店前台谈谈 看他知道些什么
All right. I'm gonna talk to the hotel clerk,see what he knows.]]>
<![CDATA[大家哪去了
Hey. Where did everybody go?]]>
<![CDATA[追踪吸血鬼
Tracking that vamp.]]>
<![CDATA[我觉得房子附近有问题
Well,I think we got a problem a lot closer to home.]]>
<![CDATA[看看这个
Look at this.]]>
<![CDATA[看见那个蓝色厢车了吗
See that blue van?]]>
<![CDATA[我哥看见那车昨天在旅店外边
My brother saw it outside the hotel yesterday.]]>
<![CDATA[我们觉得他和被拘押的吸血鬼是一伙的
We think he's working with the vampire we popped.]]>
<![CDATA[看来我们要捕猎了
Looks like we're going huntin'.]]>
<![CDATA[很高兴再见到你
Ahh. Nice to see you again.]]>
<![CDATA[是 我怀疑 听着 我要知道
Yeah,I bet. Listen,I need to know]]>
<![CDATA[昨天是谁入住215房
Who,uh,checked into room 215 yesterday.]]>
<![CDATA[215号
215.]]>
<![CDATA[是个穿连帽衫的人
It was some guy wearing a hoodie,]]>
<![CDATA[很难辨认他的样子
So it was hard to make out his face.]]>
<![CDATA[也许 他刚好开一辆蓝色厢车吗
He drive a blue van, by any chance?]]>
<![CDATA[我像是贴身男仆吗
Do I look like a valet?]]>
<![CDATA[他拿走了其中一个
He took one of those.]]>
<![CDATA[哪一个
Which one?]]>
<![CDATA[上面有"旅馆"的那个
The one that says "Lodge" On it.]]>
<![CDATA[康维斯普林斯旅馆
"Conway springs lodge."]]>
<![CDATA[夏季的时候很大的一家
Yep,big during the summer season.]]>
<![CDATA[但每年这个时节 都是关闭的
But this time of year, it's closed.]]>
<![CDATA[离这有多远
How far away is it from here?]]>
<![CDATA[几英里路程
Oh,it's a couple miles down the road.]]>
<![CDATA[你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?!]]>
<![CDATA[回答我
Answer me!]]>
<![CDATA[把它拿开
please make it go away.]]>
<![CDATA[太刺眼了
It hurts so much.]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What? Wha...]]>
<![CDATA[不 关掉 太亮了
No,shut them off! They're too bright!]]>
<![CDATA[除非你告诉我到底怎么回事
Not till you tell me what the hell's going on here.]]>
<![CDATA[我不知道
I don't know!]]>
<![CDATA[我怎么了
what's happening to me?]]>
<![CDATA[过来
Come here.]]>
<![CDATA[你以前从没这样过吗
That's never happened to you before?]]>
<![CDATA[不 没有 我肯定出什么事了
No. No,there's something wrong with me.]]>
<![CDATA[那个人 对我做了什么
That --that guy, he did something to me.]]>
<![CDATA[-什么人  -不知道
-What guy? -I don't know!]]>
<![CDATA[开蓝色厢车的人 他抓了我
This guy in a blue van, he --he grabbed me.]]>
<![CDATA[把我带到这
He took me here.]]>
<![CDATA[我的胃
oh,my stomach.]]>
<![CDATA[太难受了
It hurts so much.]]>
<![CDATA[迪恩
Dean!]]>
<![CDATA[把枪拿开 我们好谈谈
Put those away, and we can talk.]]>
<![CDATA[你为什么和杀了我爸爸的吸血鬼在一起
Why are you with the vampire that killed my dad?]]>
<![CDATA[你找错对象了
You're barking up the wrong tree.]]>
<![CDATA[她没杀你们的爸爸
She didn't kill your pops.]]>
<![CDATA[我不想伤害你 迪恩 但你不让开 别怪我不客气
I don't want to hurt you,Dean, but I will if you don't move.]]>
<![CDATA[听我说 克丽丝
Listen to me,Krissy.]]>
<![CDATA[她是无辜的
She's innocent.]]>
<![CDATA[你怎么知道
And how would you know that?]]>
<![CDATA[因为她才变成吸血鬼 一两天
Because she's fresh made, a day or two.]]>
<![CDATA[他爸爸一个月前被杀的
Her dad was killed months ago.]]>
<![CDATA[回想所有的事
This whole thing stinks.]]>
<![CDATA[我们昨晚杀的那个吸血鬼
That vamp that we killed last night?]]>
<![CDATA[为什么他对天发誓不是他干的
Why was he swearing that he didn't do it?]]>
<![CDATA[因为他是骗子
Because he was a liar.]]>
<![CDATA[吸血鬼从不乞求活命 他们只会攻击
Vampires don't beg for their lives. They attack.]]>
<![CDATA[之前我很客气地要求你
Look,last time I'm gonna ask you nicely.]]>
<![CDATA[别用枪指着我 否则会有人受伤的
Take the damn guns off me, or somebody's gonna get hurt.]]>
<![CDATA[说大话
Big talk.]]>
<![CDATA[我知道 不是吗
I know. It is,isn't it?]]>
<![CDATA[就算这个不是杀了我爸的吸血鬼
So,let's say this isn't the vamp who killed my dad.]]>
<![CDATA[她也是恶魔 必须要死
She's still a monster and deserves to die.]]>
<![CDATA[除非我能救她
Not if we can save her.]]>
<![CDATA[什么
What?]]>
<![CDATA[她还没吸过血
She hasn't fed yet.]]>
<![CDATA[如果找到转化她的人 用他的血就能逆转
We can reverse this if we find her maker and get his blood.]]>
<![CDATA[我们为什么在乎她
And why should we care about her?]]>
<![CDATA[就像我说的 捕猎不只是杀戮
Like I said,hunting isn't always about killing.]]>
<![CDATA[拜托
Oh,please.]]>
<![CDATA[告诫别人去吧 我们才不买账
Preach to some other choir. We're not buying it.]]>
<![CDATA[你想杀害无辜的女孩吗
You want to kill an innocent girl?!]]>
<![CDATA[我想让杀害我父亲的混蛋血债血偿
I want the blood sucker who killed my dad to pay.]]>
<![CDATA[我们一定会找到是谁干的
And we're gonna find out who that is.]]>
<![CDATA[但不能残忍地抓一个杀一个
But let's not be so bloodthirsty that just anyone will do.]]>
<![CDATA[但维克多说是她干的
But Victor says it's her.]]>
<![CDATA[我说不是
And I say it ain't!]]>
<![CDATA[咱们先把她放了
So we're gonna pack her to go,]]>
<![CDATA[然后亲自找维克多问个明白
And we're gonna ask Victor ourselves.]]>
<![CDATA[好吗
Okay?]]>
<![CDATA[你醒了 很好
You're awake. Good.]]>
<![CDATA[时间不多啊
We don't have much time.]]>
<![CDATA[干什么
For what?]]>
<![CDATA[布置一下
Picture this.]]>
<![CDATA[孩子们凯旋而归
The kids arrive home Victorious,]]>
<![CDATA[却发现你死在了客厅
Only to find you dead in their living room.]]>
<![CDATA[似乎 那被他们掀了老巢的吸血鬼们
It seems that nest of vampires they were hunting]]>
<![CDATA[来复仇了
Were seeking revenge...]]>
<![CDATA[还杀了你
...And killed you.]]>
<![CDATA[如此一来 他们会继续猎杀更多吸血鬼
Thus,inspiring them to hunt even more.]]>
<![CDATA[很抱歉 山姆
I'm sorry,Sam.]]>
<![CDATA[我不能让任何人毒害了我孩子们的思想
I can't have anyone poisoning my kids' minds.]]>
<![CDATA[是你在毒害他们
Other than yourself, that is.]]>
<![CDATA[我用不着你还有你那个自以为是的哥哥
I don't need to justify my actions to you]]>
<![CDATA[对我指手画脚
Or your self-righteous ass of a brother!]]>
<![CDATA[你是说和吸血鬼合作吗
You mean like why you're working with a vampire?]]>
<![CDATA[那他从中得到什么好处 随心所欲吗
So what's he get out of this? Free roaming rights?]]>
<![CDATA[这是一场战争 一场我们要输掉的战争
We are at war -- a war that we are losing.]]>
<![CDATA[利维坦惨败是个信号
That leviathan fiasco was a wake-up call.]]>
<![CDATA[我们必须尽己所能 生存下去
We have to do what we can to survive.]]>
<![CDATA[但我也没指望你能明白
But I wouldn't expect you to understand.]]>
<![CDATA[你没当过父亲
You're not a father.]]>
<![CDATA[你不会明白那种感受
You don't know what it's like]]>
<![CDATA[听着你的孩子们哭喊着死去
To hear the cries of your children dying.]]>
<![CDATA[但现在我有机会纠正这一切
But now I have a second chance to make it all right,]]>
<![CDATA[打造下一代的猎魔人
To create the next generation of hunters --]]>
<![CDATA[更强壮 更迅速 更聪明
Stronger,faster,smarter.]]>
<![CDATA[我们回来了
Hey,we're home.]]>
<![CDATA[这是怎么了
What is going on here?]]>
<![CDATA[这两个人不值得信任
These two are not to be trusted.]]>
<![CDATA[他们想毁掉我们
They're trying to destroy us.]]>
<![CDATA[你认识这吸血鬼吗 维克多
Do you know this vamp, Victor?]]>
<![CDATA[他当然认识 他俩是一伙的
Of course he does! They're working together!]]>
<![CDATA[真的吗
Is that true?]]>
<![CDATA[这很复杂
It's complicated.]]>
<![CDATA[不 其实一点也不
No,actually, it's not.]]>
<![CDATA[开蓝色厢车的人把他们转化为吸血鬼
See,blue van here's been turning fresh vamps]]>
<![CDATA[然后设计他们 让孩子们猎杀
And setting them up for you kids as easy kills.]]>
<![CDATA[但为什么
But why?]]>
<![CDATA[因为不是他们杀了我们的家人
Because they didn't kill our families,did they?]]>
<![CDATA[不是
No.]]>
<![CDATA[那是谁干的
Well,then who did?]]>
<![CDATA[我干的
I did.]]>
<![CDATA[他们都哭喊不止
And they all screamed...]]>
<![CDATA[请求宽恕 尤其是那些小的
...And begged for mercy, especially the little ones.]]>
<![CDATA[住嘴吧 赛斯
Enough,Seth!]]>
<![CDATA[你们得明白
You have to understand.]]>
<![CDATA[我找到了让未来更美好的办法
I saw a way to make the future better.]]>
<![CDATA[但要做到 我必须做出极大的努力
But to get there, I had to do something hard.]]>
<![CDATA[他杀害那些人 是你的命令吗
He killed them off your orders?]]>
<![CDATA[你们需要动力
You needed motivation.]]>
<![CDATA[我用心观察了你们很久
I scouted each and every one of you.]]>
<![CDATA[唯有如此 才能让你们去猎杀
And knew it was the only way to get you to hunt.]]>
<![CDATA[所以你杀了我们的家人
so you killed our families?]]>
<![CDATA[我知道死亡很悲伤
I know the deaths are tragic.]]>
<![CDATA[但想想未来那些生命
But think of all the future lives]]>
<![CDATA[那些因为你们而被拯救的生命
That will now be saved because you are now together.]]>
<![CDATA[所以 这些假吸血鬼不过是你为了训练我们
So,these fake vampires were just a way for you to train us]]>
<![CDATA[而往我们脑子里灌的谎言吗
And fill our heads with lies?!]]>
<![CDATA[你难道看不到吗
Don't you see?]]>
<![CDATA[这比我们任何人都重要
This is bigger than all of us.]]>
<![CDATA[我们要学会正确处理事情
We have to learn to put things in perspective.]]>
<![CDATA[跟着我
Come with me.]]>
<![CDATA[我们会度过眼前难关的
We can get past this.]]>
<![CDATA[那真是太不幸了
That is unfortunate.]]>
<![CDATA[艾登
Aidan!]]>
<![CDATA[我们要走了
We're leaving.]]>
<![CDATA[想都别想
That's not happening.]]>
<![CDATA[你会的一切 都是我教的
I taught you everything you know.]]>
<![CDATA[别逼我伤了你
Don't make me hurt you.]]>
<![CDATA[并非如此 维克多
Not everything,Victor.]]>
<![CDATA[克丽丝 不要
Krissy,don't.]]>
<![CDATA[如果我们想为家人复仇
If we want revenge for our families' deaths,]]>
<![CDATA[他就要抵命
He gives it to us!]]>
<![CDATA[我们不杀人类
We don't kill people.]]>
<![CDATA[你们也不杀人类
You don't kill people.]]>
<![CDATA[他不是人 他是魔鬼
He's not a person. He's a monster.]]>
<![CDATA[克丽丝 不论怎么做 这结局都很难看
Krissy,this ends bad, no matter what we do.]]>
<![CDATA[没错
Exactly.]]>
<![CDATA[克丽丝 不要
Krissy,don't.]]>
<![CDATA[这是为了我父亲
This is for my dad.]]>
<![CDATA[这是为了约瑟芬的家人
For Josephine's family.]]>
<![CDATA[为了艾登
For Aidan.]]>
<![CDATA[为了我
For me.]]>
<![CDATA[怎么 要留他一条命吗
So,we're just gonna let him live?]]>
<![CDATA[是啊
Yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[孤独一人 直至终老
All alone,with himself.]]>
<![CDATA[没有家人 没有朋友
No family. No friends.]]>
<![CDATA[在我看来 是很严酷的惩罚了
Ask me, that's not much of anything.]]>
<![CDATA[咱们去救那个女孩
Let's save that girl.]]>
<![CDATA[有枪
Gun!]]>
<![CDATA[慢慢喝一点
Just drink slowly.]]>
<![CDATA[这会带走那些疼痛
This will take away all the pain.]]>
<![CDATA[为你骄傲
Proud of you.]]>
<![CDATA[闭嘴 小心我揍你
Shut up, before I punch you.]]>
<![CDATA[她情况如何了
So,how's she doing?]]>
<![CDATA[好多了
Better now.]]>
<![CDATA[我想 这个是你的
I think this is yours.]]>
<![CDATA[谢谢
Thank you.]]>
<![CDATA[我在外面等
I'll wait outside.]]>
<![CDATA[好了
Okay.]]>
<![CDATA[等你准备好了 我们在车里等
Whenever you're ready, we'll be in the car.]]>
<![CDATA[你在说什么
What are you talking about?]]>
<![CDATA[你姨妈 辛辛那提 正常生活
Your aunt? Cincinnati? Normal life?]]>
<![CDATA[明天午餐时间我们就能到
We'll be there by lunch tomorrow.]]>
<![CDATA[听着 虽然我们很诡异地聚在一起 但...
Look,I hate how we were put together,but...]]>
<![CDATA[我得承认 感觉却很对
I can't deny that it feels right.]]>
<![CDATA[我又何必因为维克多而毁了这一切
And why should I let Victor ruin that,too?]]>
<![CDATA[所以 你要说的是
So, what you're saying is that]]>
<![CDATA[你喜欢那边的小子 不想离开这是吗
You like that boy over there and you want to stay?]]>
<![CDATA[什么 艾登吗 不
What? Aidan? No.]]>
<![CDATA[他更像是兄弟
I mean... He's like my brother.]]>
<![CDATA[才不是那样呢
It's nothing like that.]]>
<![CDATA[你们都还未成年
Well, you're all still minors.]]>
<![CDATA[没多久了
Not for long.]]>
<![CDATA[约瑟芬几个月后就18岁了
Josephine will be 18 in a few months.]]>
<![CDATA[我们在这有自己的生活 有彼此
And we all have a life and each other here.]]>
<![CDATA[还有猎魔吗
And hunting?]]>
<![CDATA[我们不会主动出击
We won't go looking for it.]]>
<![CDATA[但如果有怪物出现嘛
But if any monsters show up around here,]]>
<![CDATA[他们最好小心了
They better look out.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧 很好
Okay. Good.]]>
<![CDATA[真的吗
Really?]]>
<![CDATA[我还以为我得跟你抗争一下呢
I thought I was gonna have to fight you way more on that.]]>
<![CDATA[你说得没错 你不再是孩子了
Well,you're right. You're not a kid anymore.]]>
<![CDATA[可以自己做决定
You can make your own decisions.]]>
<![CDATA[你这老头子还挺通情达理
You're all right for an old guy.]]>
<![CDATA[我才不老
I'm really not that old.]]>
<![CDATA[你就骗自己吧
You keep telling yourself that.]]>
<![CDATA[好吧
All right.]]>
<![CDATA[我会找个人 隔段时间
Well,I'm gonna have a,uh -- a guy come and check on you]]>
<![CDATA[就来看看你 好吗
Every once in a while, okay?]]>
<![CDATA[他叫加斯
His name is Garth.]]>
<![CDATA[他会确保你一切都好 生活无忧
He'll make sure that you're all right and you got what you need.]]>
<![CDATA[-加斯  -是的
-Garth? -Yeah.]]>
<![CDATA[一开始你会觉得他怪怪的 以后就会喜欢他的
He's a little strange at first, but you'll come to love him.]]>
<![CDATA[你保重 迪恩
Take care,Dean.]]>
<![CDATA[是 迪恩再见了
Yeah. Goodbye,Dean.]]>
<![CDATA[艾登
Aidan.]]>
<![CDATA[听好了
Listen,there's,uh,]]>
<![CDATA[关于克丽丝 有点事我要告诉你
Something I want to tell you about Krissy.]]>
<![CDATA[我知道 知道
I know. I know.]]>
<![CDATA[我要是敢伤了她 你就杀了我
You'll kill me if I ever hurt her.]]>
<![CDATA[如此这般 这般如此
Blah. Blah. Blah.]]>
<![CDATA[不 不是 她会杀了你
No,no. No. She'll kill you.]]>
<![CDATA[祝你好运
Good luck.]]>
<![CDATA[很不错
This is good.]]>
<![CDATA[不是吗
Is it?]]>
<![CDATA[本来会很糟糕
Could have been a lot worse.]]>
<![CDATA[再不关掉那地狱之门 就真糟糕了
Will be if we don't shut those gates of hell soon.]]>
<![CDATA[那他们以后会如何
What do they have to do with any of that?]]>
<![CDATA[他们现在也是猎魔人了
They're hunters now.]]>
<![CDATA[这条路不是说脱身就脱身的
You don't just walk away from that.]]>
<![CDATA[想脱身只有一个办法
There's only one way out of that,]]>
<![CDATA[你我都知道 那办法不容易
And you and I both know it ain't pretty.]]>
<![CDATA[也许他们会不同
Maybe they'll be different.]]>
<![CDATA[也许我们关掉地狱之门 就一劳永逸了
Or maybe if we shut that hell hole once and for and all,]]>
<![CDATA[那三个孩子就能过上真正的生活
Those three can have a real life.]]>
<![CDATA[也许不止他们三个
Maybe they won't be the only ones.]]>